Guide to the Johnson family papers, 1776-1937
Johnson family papers, 1776-1937
- Series IV. Digital Images
  - Digital Images of the Contents of Box 3
  - Digital Images of the Contents of Box 4
  - Digital Images of the Contents of Box 5
  - Digital Images of the Contents of Box 6
  - Digital Images of the Contents of Box 7
SEPARATED MATERIAL
Publications Removed From Collection 4928 - To Be Cataloged Separately:
Bible. Philadelphia: John Thompson and Abraham Small, 1798.
Cornell, Mary Emily. The Autobiography of M.E. Cornell. Ithaca, New York: The Cayuga Press, 1929.
Horace. The Works of Horace. 2 volumes. Edinburgh: J. Dickson and C. Elliot, 1783.
Icones Biblicae. Strassburg: 1625-30.
Johnson, A. B. Deep Sea Soundings and Explorations of the Bottom. Boston: John Wilson and Son, 1861.
Miller, Samuel F. The Supreme Court of the United States: A Series of Biographies. Washington, D.C.: W. H. Barnes and Co., 1877.
Ovid. Metamorphosis. Amsterdam (?): 1675.
The Salem Book. Salem, New York: Salem Review Press, 1896.
Wyman, T. B. Genealogy of the Name and Family of Hunt. Boston: John Wilson and Son, 1862-63.
Zorn, Walter Lewis. The Descendants of the Presidents of the United States of America. Monroe, Michigan: Walter Lewis Zorn, 1954.